Philip Singer Papers
Philip Singer Papers
- Films
  - Ischia
    - Recordings
      - [Ischia] #1, description on tape reads, "Mayor Barand Ricardo - Restaurant."; singer_p_0357; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] #2, description on tape reads, "School teachers, Cassamicciolo - journalism, Forio Mayor"; singer_p_0363; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] #2, description on tape reads, "Ricardo - Christina."; singer_p_0358; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] #2 & #5, singer_p_0361; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] #3, description on tape reads, "David - camera, Giovanni - Bar, German war"; singer_p_0359; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] #3, description on tape reads, "Mayor Forio, German consultant"; singer_p_0364; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] #4, description on tape reads, "Tourist director, Gafa editor, [illegible], cafe owner, printer, bar - MJ and son"; singer_p_0360; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] #4, description on tape reads, "Milan fair, shots of Ischia German [signs?]"; singer_p_0365; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] #5, description on tape reads, "Anthropology - German hotel objects - Naples"; singer_p_0366; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] 1 of 2, 1997; singer_p_0367; raw footage; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Ischia] 2 of 2, 1997; singer_p_0368; raw footage; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
  - Juan Farre Productions, Singer worked with this studio
    - Frida Kahlo Narrative Therapy, 2008 (Box 4)
    - General, 2007 (Box 4)
    - General, 2008 (Box 5)
    - Immigration, 2007 (Box 5)
    - Invidia, 2006 (Box 5)
    - La Malinche, 2008 (Box 5)
    - Nino Fidencio, 2006-2008 (Box 5)
    - Nino Fidencio, De Roma a Espinazo, 2009 (Box 7)
    - Recordings, small differences of the DVD artwork suggest that there may be differences in content, thus multiple versions of titles were kept
      - Cooperativas Sin Fronteras: Documental "El Primer Paso", singer_p_1027; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Cooperativas Sin Fronteras: Documental "El Primer Paso", singer_p_1028; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Cooperativas Sin Fronteras: Documental "El Primer Paso", singer_p_1029; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Cooperativas Sin Fronteras: Documental "El Primer Paso", singer_p_1030; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 1 y 2, singer_p_1003; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 10, singer_p_1008; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 11 y 12, singer_p_1009; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 13 y 14, singer_p_1010; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 14.1, singer_p_1011; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 14.2 y 18, singer_p_1012; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 21, singer_p_1014; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 3 y 4, singer_p_1004; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 5, singer_p_1005; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 6 y 7, singer_p_1006; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Documental Nino Fidencio Espinazo N.L. MiniDV 8 y 9, singer_p_1007; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Farre Discussion, singer_p_1349; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 53)
      - Farre Discussion, singer_p_1350; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 53)
      - Farre Discussion, singer_p_1373; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 54)
      - Nino Fidencio, singer_p_1246; label on disc reads, "Entrevista a los, Lic. Juan Farre y Lic. Curry Farre, Programa "Dia a Dia"; DVD; running time 40:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Nino Fidencio from Rome to Espinazo, singer_p_1316; with English subtitles; DVD; running time 89:00 (Box 52)
      - Nino Fidencio from Rome to Espinazo, singer_p_1118; with English subtitles; DVD; running time 89:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Nino Fidencio from Rome to Espinazo, singer_p_1119; Spanish only, brief synopsis; DVD; running time 89:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Nino Fidencio from Rome to Espinazo, singer_p_1120; Spanish cut-down; DVD; running time 89:00 (Box 52)
      - Nino Fidencio from Rome to Espinazo, singer_p_1140; English subtitles; DVD; running time 89:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Nino Fidencio from Rome to Espinazo [Copy 1], singer_p_1152; with English subtitles, press kit trailer; DVD; running time 02:00 (Box 52)
      - Nino Fidencio from Rome to Espinazo [Copy 2], singer_p_1153; with English subtitles, press kit trailer; DVD; running time 02:00 (Box 52)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1016; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; promotion material; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1017; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; promotion material; DVD; running time 87:00 (Box 51)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1018; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; English version; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1019; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; English version; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1020; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1021; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; in Spanish with English subtitles; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
        Description of film on back of case reads: "Nino Fidencio, a healer who lived his life taking care of the ill in the recondite town of the northeastern desert called Espinazo, Nuevo Leon, had thousands of followers, whom, still living, already gave him the status of a miraculous saint; an exceptional human being, a God-sent for treatment and comfort. When Fidencio died, in 1938, a growing religion began to form, that with time, expanded and gained strength. Nowadays, there are thousands of fidencistas scattered around the country."
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1022; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; in Spanish with English subtitles; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 51)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1154; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; case is wrapped in cellophane; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 52)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1155; tagline in Spanish, translated into English: "Let the rich people go to Rome, everybody else will go to Espinazo"; case is wrapped in cellophane; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 52)
      - Nino Fidencio: De Roma a Espinazo, singer_p_1156; full description in Spanish is on back of case; DVD; running time 87:00 (Box 52)
      - Who Am I? Who Are You?, singer_p_1158; label on disc reads, "Three films for / by youth: Box of Life, Eyes Shut (Identity), Illusion (Pain)"; DVD; running time 08:00 (Box 52)
      - Who Am I? Who Are You?, singer_p_1159; label on disc reads, "Three films for / by youth: Box of Life, Eyes Shut (Identity), Illusion (Pain)"; DVD; running time 08:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Who Am I? Who Are You?, singer_p_1160; label on disc reads, "Three films for / by youth: Box of Life, Eyes Shut (Identity), Illusion (Pain)"; DVD; running time 08:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Who Am I? Who Are You?, singer_p_1369; three films for and by youth: "Box of Life," "Eyes Shut (Identity)," "Illusion (Pain)"; DVD; running time 08:00 (Box 54)
  - Kali Mai Film
    - Script and synopsis, 2015 (Box 5)
  - Kali of East New York
    - Script, undated (Box 5)
  - The Last Interview of Thomas Szasz
    - Cover art, 2013 (Box 5)
    - Review, 2013 (Box 5)
    - Recordings
      - Szasz [Thomas] #3, 2002; singer_p_1304; DVD; running time 90:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Szasz #2, singer_p_1352; note on case reads, "'Demolishing psychiatry,' 'Common Sense,' and Szasz; DVD; running time 59:00 (Box 53)
      - The Last Interview of Thomas Szasz, M.D., singer_p_1105; DVD; running time 50:00 (Box 51)
        Description on DVD reads, "Thomas Szasz, M.D. famously challenged modern psychiatry in his book The Myth of Mental Illness, saying that the profession was largely pseudoscience. In this edited interview, recorded just two years before his death, he discusses the intellectual foundations of his theories, and why these theories are so threatening to the psychiatric establishment. In addition, he himself is challenged by Dr. Singer, the interviewer, to back his controversial claims."
      - The Last Interview of Thomas Szasz, M.D., singer_p_1117; DVD; running time 30:00 (Oversize 5)
  - The Last Mattanza
    - Articles, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Articles and maps, 1998-1999 (Box 23)
    - Book proposal, undated; chapters 1-7 with sysnopsis (Box 5)
    - David Plath, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Day 1, 1998 (Box 5)
    - English outline, 2001-2004 (Box 5)
    - Favignana and Aldo Bua, 1994; 1999-2001 (Box 5)
    - Favignana: La Mattanza essay, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Gioacchino Cataldo interview, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Gioacchino Ernandes ("Old Rais") inverview, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Gioacchino Ernandes ("Old Rais") National Geographic inverview, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Italian summary, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Log days 1-23, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Maggio, 1998-2001 (Box 6)
    - Map guides, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 23)
    - Prospero Sanna, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Review, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Rocco Ponzio interview, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Sabino, undated (Box 6)
    - Salvatore Spataro, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Summary sheets, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Tonnaroti interviews with notes, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Tuna, 1998-2015 (Box 6)
    - Tuna fishing in Sicily - "La Pesca Del Tonno in Sicilia", undated; bound and in Italian (Oversize 7)
    - Vincenzo Zabbarino interview, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Websites, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Websites, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Websites, 1998 (Box 23)
    - Recordings, contains both English and Italian versions of film
      - Favignana, 04/02/2009; singer_p_0406; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
      - Favignana #1, 04/28/2007; singer_p_0423; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
      - Favignana Tonnara: Return of the 100-Year-Old Museum Wooden Boats, First Cooperative Year 1997 (Raw), singer_p_1339; DVD; running time 70:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Favignana Tonnara: Return of the 100-Year-Old Museum Wooden Boats, First Cooperative Year 1997 (Raw), singer_p_1340; DVD; running time 70:00 (Oversize 6)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #1, 1996; label on tape provides this description: "Favignana - 1st day; tuna preparations; interviews with Bua. Hotel, Baker; Panorama; Dasquales rest. Pescadira food"; singer_p_0277; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #2, 1996; label on tape provides this description: "Preparation - Tuna"; singer_p_0278; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #2, Life Hy, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "RHS - 3/8/97, Interview old Rais, old days"; singer_p_0310; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #3, 1996; label on tape provides this description: "Camraria, boats"; singer_p_0279; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #3, Preps, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Interview with Castiglione"; singer_p_0301; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #4, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Boats"; singer_p_0280; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #5, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Nets"; singer_p_0281; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #6, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Nets"; singer_p_0282; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #7, 1997; singer_p_0283; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #8, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Leo - Plains, trap"; singer_p_0284; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #9, 1997; singer_p_0285; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #10, 1997; singer_p_0286; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #11, 1997; singer_p_0287; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #12, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Preparing boat for RAIS - see also #9"; singer_p_0288; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #13, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Coppa in boat"; singer_p_0289; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #14, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Too much Sirocco deferred to 5/19 today, taking of the coppa from storage; flowers in the net"; singer_p_0290; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #15, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Rais interview, Diving interview; Worker discussion re: pay, etc."; singer_p_0291; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #16, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Rais boat - sound only last 3:00; fisherman discussion"; singer_p_0292; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #17, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Interview with fisherman"; singer_p_0293; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #18, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Coppa in sea, part 1"; singer_p_0294; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #19, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Coppa in sea, part 2"; singer_p_0295; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #20, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Name of Jesus"; singer_p_0296; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] #21, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "After Mattanza, old stabil"; singer_p_0297; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Chi Gong, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Linda 1/97"; singer_p_0302; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Mattanza (Part 1 of 2), 1997; singer_p_0298; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Mattanza (Part 2 of 2), 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Castiglione butcher of tuna"; singer_p_0299; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Stabil, 1997; singer_p_0300; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Stabil #1, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Stabil - locations, disc of changes/restorations of stabil; Camparia"; singer_p_0303; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Stabil #2, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Blips - send to Panasonic"; singer_p_0304; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Stabil #5, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Boats - audio - send to Panasonic"; singer_p_0305; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Stabil #6, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Parodi - boats"; singer_p_0306; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Stabil #7, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Boats 3/17/97"; singer_p_0307; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Stabil #9, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Stabil Maestri-Daschi"; singer_p_0308; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - [The Last Mattanza] Stabil #10, 1997; label on tape provides this description: "Stabil - Maestro says we can't go in"; singer_p_0309; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 44)
      - Mattanza, 1997/04/10; singer_p_1277; interview with Ponzo, Rocco, Francasca; CD; running time 15:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Mattanza, 1992/09/18; singer_p_1278; text on disc reads, "Gioachino Cataldo, Vincenzo Zabarino"; CD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Mattanza, 1987; singer_p_1284; text on disc reads, "Notobartalo vo., Pesca Del Tonno, Favignana underwater scenes"; DVD; running time 70:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Mattanza (1 of 5), handwritten text on case reads, "Intro - the nets diagram explained. Day 1-2-3 (school children), 4 ([illegible] nets by business), 5 (anchors), 6 (singing 1:38)"; singer_p_1387; DVD; running time 114:00 (Box 55)
      - Mattanza (Part 2 of 5), singer_p_1255; text on case reads, "begin with day 7, Tonnaroti eat fish, [illegible] eat fish delicately, setting nets - buoys in sea"; DVD; running time 100:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Mattanza (Part 4 of 5), singer_p_1256; text on case reads, "VG film/audio - keep VHS, shot of Madonna and tuna, old [illegible]"; DVD; running time 95:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Mattanza (Raw), singer_p_1338; text on case reads, "Old Rais - Gioachino; stabilimonto - fixing old boats; interview with Zabarino - cooperative; nets (old rais)"; DVD; running time 52:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Mattanza (Raw) Old Rais, handwritten text on case reads, "Gioachino and men; boats launching, pulling in, bailing, nets; :30 - Cusumano talks about 1935 boats, Mattanza future; boat repairs [blank], caulking; interviews: 1:04 - 1:09, interview boat builder [1:20], boats [1:46]"; singer_p_1337; DVD; running time 118:00 (Box 53)
      - Mattanza (Raw) Old Rais / New Rais, handwritten text on case reads, "New rais and old rais (catalix), the cooperative [luik (sic) and my fight for payback] [see CD for my interview with Cataldo]. The wooden boats and the region, school children - by order of region access to boats was stopped"; singer_p_1386; DVD; running time 91:00 (Box 55)
      - Mattanza Favignana Italy, singer_p_1334; National Geographic edit; DVD; running time 23:00 (Box 53)
      - Mattanza Favignana Italy (National Geographic Edit), singer_p_1059; DVD; running time 23:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Mattanza Favignana Italy (National Geographic Edit), singer_p_1060; DVD; running time 23:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Mattanza Favignana Italy (National Geographic edit), singer_p_1563; DVD; running time 23:00 (Box 43)
      - Mattanza Notobara Tolo "La Pesca Del Tonno", singer_p_1389; DVD; running time 30:00 (Box 55)
      - Mattanza Wooden Boats, singer_p_1357; DVD; running time 120:00 (Box 53)
      - Mattanza Wooden Boats (Part 1 of 2), singer_p_1254; museum antiques brought to life, the cooperative; DVD; running time 49:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Mattanza: Wooden Boat Anti Ques Brought To Life (copy 1), singer_p_1056; label on disc reads, "The first cooperative"; DVD; running time 180:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Mattanza: Wooden Boat Anti Ques Brought To Life (copy 2), singer_p_1057; label on disc reads, "The first cooperative"; DVD; running time 180:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Mattanza: Wooden Boat Anti Ques Brought To Life (copy 3), singer_p_1058; label on disc reads, "The first cooperative"; DVD; running time 180:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Mattanza: Wooden Boat Antiques Brought to Life, singer_p_1279; text on disc reads, "The first cooperative"; DVD; running time 180:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Old Rais / Spataro Salvatore, 1997; singer_p_0813; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Box 49)
      - Old Rais, Spataro, 1992/06/10; singer_p_1276; DVD; running time 11:00 (Oversize 6)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, singer_p_1336; English edit; DVD; running time 113:00 (Box 53)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza (1 of 5), singer_p_1328; DVD; running time 115:00 (Oversize 6)
        An itemized list of contents are documented on the case. The list reads, "Rais (first contact); men prepare cords - talk; prepare cord; putting boat in water; tufa; school comes; Gluachinno talks to pupils; Castio and business inspect nets; loading boat (1:10); carpentry, anchors (1:20-26), sing (1:36) [working with nets]."
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza (1 of 5), singer_p_1329; handwritten text on disc reads, "not finalized"; DVD; running time 115:00 (Oversize 6)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza (2 of 5), singer_p_1330; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 6)
        An itemized list of contents are documented on the case. The list reads, "Tonnauli - milling about - talking, food prep in [illegible], loading nets - illegible], cooking/eating; [day 8] [day 9] retired old (101 bar-cafe 102), moving boat; [day 10] setting net and buoys in water (1:12 -->1:23 --> 1:38 dark good)."
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza (3 of 5), singer_p_1331; DVD; running time 84:00 (Box 53)
        An itemized list of contents are documented on the case. The list reads, "Day 11 - empty boats, loading tufa, tonaaroti talk on boat (casual), good shot - many nets [28:00], hands (38:00), sing (47:00 - 54:00)."
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza (4 of 5), singer_p_1332; DVD; running time 94:00 (Oversize 6)
        An itemized list of contents are documented on the case. The list reads, "Day 14-18 - Rais and fisherman (hanging [illegible]), nets, Rais interview, [illegible] gets dressed; rowing, moist tuna at dock, men sit and talk - joke; setting nets for 'camera del morse (:38 - good squad); net tangle at sea (1:08) interviews - keep mattanza?; chanta and hooks - pay -- virgin and tuna."
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza (5 of 5), singer_p_1333; DVD; running time 46:00 (Box 53)
        An itemized list of contents are documented on the case. The list reads, "Interview: Giuarminno [Italian], day 22 - archive pics, tourists, fisherman sing 'Al Amore' at death net, castiglione boat."
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, 1 of 3, singer_p_0064; additional text on tape reads, "63 Tonnaroti 22 Giorni"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 30)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, 3 of 3, singer_p_0065; additional text on tape reads, "63 Tonnaroti 22 Giorni"; VHS; running time 75:00 (Box 30)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, 3 of 5, singer_p_0068; additional text on tape reads, "63 Tonnaroti 22 Giorni"; VHS; running time 94:00 (Box 30)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, 4 of 5, singer_p_0067; additional text on tape reads, "63 Tonnaroti 22 Giorni"; VHS; running time 94:00 (Box 30)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, days 11-13, 1996; singer_p_0062; possible footage for documentary film; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 29)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, days 14-21, 1996; singer_p_0063; possible footage for documentary film; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 29)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, days 7-10, 1996; singer_p_0061; possible footage for documentary film; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 29)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, English Cut-down (Master), singer_p_0071; VHS; running time 113:00 (Box 30)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, English edit, singer_p_0069; VHS; running time 113:00 (Box 30)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, English edit, singer_p_0070; VHS; running time 113:00 (Box 30)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, Part 1 of 5, singer_p_0059; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 29)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, part 2 of 5, singer_p_0060; VHS; running time 99:00 (Box 29)